[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 17, "question": "Is it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 18, "answer": "That's absolutely rude.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "absolutely", "rude", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "How important strategically is winning Ohio?", "question_tokens": ["How", "important", "strategically", "is", "winning", "Ohio", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "RB", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "You know, we'd definitely like a win.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "we", "'d", "definitely", "like", "a", "win", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Ohio"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 70, "question": "I mean, does he feel like he takes two steps forward then two back and so on, that it's been a real uphill battle when he wasn't maybe expecting it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "does", "he", "feel", "like", "he", "takes", "two", "steps", "forward", "then", "two", "back", "and", "so", "on", ",", "that", "it", "'s", "been", "a", "real", "uphill", "battle", "when", "he", "was", "n't", "maybe", "expecting", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "CD", "RB", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 71, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP"], "qSentId": 81, "question": "Why do they're not getting the real Mitt Romney, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "do", "they", "'re", "not", "getting", "the", "real", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "I think he's not on the PIERS", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "'s", "not", "on", "the", "PIERS"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 149, "question": "Why have you resisted me for so long?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "have", "you", "resisted", "me", "for", "so", "long", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 150, "answer": "I haven't resisted your charms at all.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "n't", "resisted", "your", "charms", "at", "all", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 153, "question": "Tell me about the reality of being a presidential candidate because it's incredibly hard work, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "about", "the", "reality", "of", "being", "a", "presidential", "candidate", "because", "it", "'s", "incredibly", "hard", "work", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 154, "answer": "It is, it is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", ",", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 166, "question": "Will it be a determining day, do you think, or are we going to be here in a month with things still undecided?", "question_tokens": ["Will", "it", "be", "a", "determining", "day", ",", "do", "you", "think", ",", "or", "are", "we", "going", "to", "be", "here", "in", "a", "month", "with", "things", "still", "undecided", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 167, "answer": "My opinion is, I think it will be a determining day because there's so many delegates up for grabs.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "opinion", "is", ",", "I", "think", "it", "will", "be", "a", "determining", "day", "because", "there", "'s", "so", "many", "delegates", "up", "for", "grabs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 178, "question": "And it maybe that if Mitt Romney was to prevails here or Rick Santorum, it helps them to have this long battle?", "question_tokens": ["And", "it", "maybe", "that", "if", "Mitt", "Romney", "was", "to", "prevails", "here", "or", "Rick", "Santorum", ",", "it", "helps", "them", "to", "have", "this", "long", "battle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "NNS", "RB", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 179, "answer": "Well, the process is very good.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "process", "is", "very", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney", "Rick Santorum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 196, "question": "Are you disappointed that there is no bona fide Tea Party candidate left in the race?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "disappointed", "that", "there", "is", "no", "bona", "fide", "Tea", "Party", "candidate", "left", "in", "the", "race", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 197, "answer": "I am very happy to get behind any of these candidates because I want to have a unifying voice.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "very", "happy", "to", "get", "behind", "any", "of", "these", "candidates", "because", "I", "want", "to", "have", "a", "unifying", "voice", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Santorum", "Mitt Romney", "Newt Gingrich", "Ron Paul"]}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 204, "question": "Would that be a misreading?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "that", "be", "a", "misreading", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 205, "answer": "I like Rick Santorum a lot but I like Mitt Romney, I like Newt Gingrich, I like Ron Paul.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "like", "Rick", "Santorum", "a", "lot", "but", "I", "like", "Mitt", "Romney", ",", "I", "like", "Newt", "Gingrich", ",", "I", "like", "Ron", "Paul", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Who do you most agree with?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "most", "agree", "with", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "JJS", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "I think -- I think my opinions were fairly forthright throughout the debate and I felt, quite honestly, I was the perfect candidate for America.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "my", "opinions", "were", "fairly", "forthright", "throughout", "the", "debate", "and", "I", "felt", ",", "quite", "honestly", ",", "I", "was", "the", "perfect", "candidate", "for", "America", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 227, "question": "I mean if you're so vehemently in the vanguard against Obama care, presumably Mitt Romney is the least of the four candidates that you would personally endorse, right?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "if", "you", "'re", "so", "vehemently", "in", "the", "vanguard", "against", "Obama", "care", ",", "presumably", "Mitt", "Romney", "is", "the", "least", "of", "the", "four", "candidates", "that", "you", "would", "personally", "endorse", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", ",", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "Well --", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "VBP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "RBR", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "Michele Bachmann, were you as appalled as I was by Rush Limbaugh's rhetoric?", "question_tokens": ["Michele", "Bachmann", ",", "were", "you", "as", "appalled", "as", "I", "was", "by", "Rush", "Limbaugh", "'s", "rhetoric", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Well, what I thought at first is that this is a 3D example of what Obama care is going to mean in every America's life from now on because essentially for the first time in the history of the country we have one person who will be a health care czar, who will not only dictate what we get in health care but more importantly what we won't get in health care.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "what", "I", "thought", "at", "first", "is", "that", "this", "is", "a", "3D", "example", "of", "what", "Obama", "care", "is", "going", "to", "mean", "in", "every", "America", "'s", "life", "from", "now", "on", "because", "essentially", "for", "the", "first", "time", "in", "the", "history", "of", "the", "country", "we", "have", "one", "person", "who", "will", "be", "a", "health", "care", "czar", ",", "who", "will", "not", "only", "dictate", "what", "we", "get", "in", "health", "care", "but", "more", "importantly", "what", "we", "wo", "n't", "get", "in", "health", "care", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michele Bachmann"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "VBZ", "IN", ":"], "qSentId": 306, "question": "Right?", "question_tokens": ["Right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 307, "answer": "No, what I'm saying is that --", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "what", "I", "'m", "saying", "is", "that", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 348, "question": "Do you think homosexuality is a sin?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "homosexuality", "is", "a", "sin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 349, "answer": "I think that it's -- it's unnatural.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "it", "'s", "--", "it", "'s", "unnatural", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 358, "question": "What do you think of his comments?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "his", "comments", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 359, "answer": "Well, I'm not -- I'm here as a member of Congress.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "--", "I", "'m", "here", "as", "a", "member", "of", "Congress", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "But do you agree with him?", "question_tokens": ["But", "do", "you", "agree", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "I am not here as anybody's judge.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "am", "not", "here", "as", "anybody", "'s", "judge", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "This is one of the fastest sea changes in public opinion that people can remember in America, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["This", "is", "one", "of", "the", "fastest", "sea", "changes", "in", "public", "opinion", "that", "people", "can", "remember", "in", "America", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "Well, there is still -- every state in the country that has put this up to the vote, people have voted for marriage between a man and a woman.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "there", "is", "still", "--", "every", "state", "in", "the", "country", "that", "has", "put", "this", "up", "to", "the", "vote", ",", "people", "have", "voted", "for", "marriage", "between", "a", "man", "and", "a", "woman", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 431, "question": "Just equality of respect?", "question_tokens": ["Just", "equality", "of", "respect", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 432, "answer": "I believe that everyone under the law here in the United States has the right to the same level of protections under our Constitution.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "believe", "that", "everyone", "under", "the", "law", "here", "in", "the", "United", "States", "has", "the", "right", "to", "the", "same", "level", "of", "protections", "under", "our", "Constitution", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Would you agree with those comments, personally?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "agree", "with", "those", "comments", ",", "personally", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Honestly, I think I have had enough of the conversation.", "answer_tokens": ["Honestly", ",", "I", "think", "I", "have", "had", "enough", "of", "the", "conversation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "It is a lively horse, though, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "is", "a", "lively", "horse", ",", "though", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", ",", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "For you.", "answer_tokens": ["For", "you", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Is it snobbery to want your kids to go to college?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "snobbery", "to", "want", "your", "kids", "to", "go", "to", "college", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "Everyone wants the best.", "answer_tokens": ["Everyone", "wants", "the", "best", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 533, "question": "Was he wrong to use that word?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "he", "wrong", "to", "use", "that", "word", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 534, "answer": "Listen, Piers, I have been a mother of 28 children from every level of capability.", "answer_tokens": ["Listen", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "have", "been", "a", "mother", "of", "28", "children", "from", "every", "level", "of", "capability", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "They're -- oh, really, Piers?", "question_tokens": ["They", "'re", "--", "oh", ",", "really", ",", "Piers", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "I'm not on the left or right.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "on", "the", "left", "or", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "Aren't you glad you did?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "n't", "you", "glad", "you", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "So respect on both sides is what we need to get to?", "question_tokens": ["So", "respect", "on", "both", "sides", "is", "what", "we", "need", "to", "get", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "Of course.", "answer_tokens": ["Of", "course", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michele Bachmann"]}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", ",", "WRB", "DT", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "What planet are we on?", "question_tokens": ["What", "planet", "are", "we", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "Lewis, I just had Michele Bachmann on, who called me rude and was indignant because I had the impertinence to suggest that she was judgmental, when some would argue she's the most judgmental woman in American politics.", "answer_tokens": ["Lewis", ",", "I", "just", "had", "Michele", "Bachmann", "on", ",", "who", "called", "me", "rude", "and", "was", "indignant", "because", "I", "had", "the", "impertinence", "to", "suggest", "that", "she", "was", "judgmental", ",", "when", "some", "would", "argue", "she", "'s", "the", "most", "judgmental", "woman", "in", "American", "politics", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kirk Cameron"]}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 653, "question": "Did they burn their hands on Bunsen Burners?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "they", "burn", "their", "hands", "on", "Bunsen", "Burners", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 654, "answer": "I thought it was quite interesting, the reaction to the Kirk Cameron comments on my show, because I must say, I didn't expect it to erupt the way that it did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "it", "was", "quite", "interesting", ",", "the", "reaction", "to", "the", "Kirk", "Cameron", "comments", "on", "my", "show", ",", "because", "I", "must", "say", ",", "I", "did", "n't", "expect", "it", "to", "erupt", "the", "way", "that", "it", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 661, "question": "What?", "question_tokens": ["What", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "."], "aSentId": 662, "answer": "It's that whole thing of, you know -- it's -- you know, being Jewish, you know, you kind of -- I know enough about Christianity to know you're not being a Christian.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "that", "whole", "thing", "of", ",", "you", "know", "--", "it", "'s", "--", "you", "know", ",", "being", "Jewish", ",", "you", "know", ",", "you", "kind", "of", "--", "I", "know", "enough", "about", "Christianity", "to", "know", "you", "'re", "not", "being", "a", "Christian", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "Why are you worried about?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "are", "you", "worried", "about", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "It's already done.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "already", "done", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 680, "question": "What did you make up of the rush Limbaugh furor?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "up", "of", "the", "rush", "Limbaugh", "furor", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 681, "answer": "Wow.", "answer_tokens": ["Wow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1958"]}, "docId": "120305pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 685, "question": "What are your overall thoughts about this Republican race?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "your", "overall", "thoughts", "about", "this", "Republican", "race", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 686, "answer": "I think it's one of the most spectacular races I've ever watched, if it was like maybe 1958.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "one", "of", "the", "most", "spectacular", "races", "I", "'ve", "ever", "watched", ",", "if", "it", "was", "like", "maybe", "1958", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]